Eric Evans

Front-End Developer

- zipbugdev@gmail.com
 - 801-837-6106 •
 - zipbugdev.com •

Fast shouldn't mean sloppy. I work hard to bring you quick results without compromising on quality. For the past three years I've worked for great companies using the latest technologies to build pixel perfect sites.

I love to learn and grow, I constantly follow the top developers and technology companies to see what they are doing and better understand the world of the web.

Experience



Allen Communication Learning Services

Februrary 2015 - present

Build custom learning solutions for clients needs Build handlebars.js templates Assist other developers in meeting deadlines debug older software issues



ThomasARTS July 2014 - November 2014- Contract

Created sites based off of PSD designs. Maintained semantic code base Created sites in Wordpress or Drupal Worked with team to meet deadlines



Equitable Life & Casualty

Febuary 2014 - July 2014-Contract Created Basic CMS Maintain semantic code base Designed & developed responsive templates



RANLife August 2012 - Febuary 2014

Front End web design and development for the companie's desktop and mobile site. I also worked on branding, flyer, postcard design, and all other graphics that take place in the company.

SKILLS

JINIELS —						
HTML 5	•	•		•	•	
CSS 3	•	•	•	•	•	
JQuery	•	•	•	•	•	
РНР	•	•	•	•	0	
JavaScript	•	•	•	•	0	
AngularJS	•	•	•	0	0	
Photoshop	•	•	•	0	0	
Illustrator	•	•	•	0	0	
InDesign	•	•	0	0	0	
Responsive Design	•	•	•	•	0	
MySQL	•	•	•	0	0	
LAMP Stack	•	•	•	•	0	
		_				

EDUCATION



O'Reilly School of Technology 2012

Introduction to PHP Modern Javascript Certification. System Administration 1 - Bash Programming



SLCC 2010 - 2012

Associates Degree Visual Arts/Graphic Design

Reading Development Gaming Camping

ACHIEVEMENTS

Rebuilt Allen Communication's website in tandem with JIBE Media in three weeks. We reduced page load time from 6 seconds to 1 second and kept all the original images/content.

Learned ColdFusion for Equitable Life and Casualty to help the Back-End team create page templates.

Built custom learning solutions for many companies including: Avon, 7-Eleven, DIRECTV, Clearlink, etc.

Built mortgage calculator mobile app for RANLife home loans, it's currently only available on Android.